seobythesea.com 2019-05-20

# Privacy Policy for SEO by the Sea

SEO by the Sea does share some personally identifiable data to some third parties. 

Information collected by SEO by the Sea about visits to the site in SEO by the Seaâ€™s generic web logs will not be shared with others, except for the use of non-identifying and aggregated information to better the design of SEO by the Sea or attract advertisers. . 

SEO by the Sea uses [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us) and Google Webmaster tools to learn about traffic to the site and improve the services offered by the site.

SEO by the Sea offers visitors the opportunity to have their gravatar avatars displayed, and uses the WordPress site statistics which are governed by the [Automattic Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).

SEO by the Sea enables visitors to subscribe to notifications of new posts on the site, with the submission of the subscriber’s email, and that data is protected by [Google’s privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us).

Private information shared with SEO by the Sea through contact form or email or in any other method will remain private unless permission is provided to share the information, or the information is demanded through an order from the Courts or a specific legal authority of State or Federal Government with proper warrant or subpoena.

SEO by the Sea does not target nor purposefully or knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.

SEO by the Sea contains links to other websites which have their own privacy practices, and this privacy policy only applies to the pages of SEO by the Sea, and not to any other site which may be linked to by this site.

This website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your device. Our site uses cookies from third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites. You can opt-out of these cookies by using the ‘opt-out’ button here: <https://app.adroll.com/optout/safari>

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please feel free to [contact me](http://www.seobythesea.com/contact-us/).

I recommend that anyone using the Web learn more about privacy issues online, and suggest the following resources as good places to begin to find out more on the topic:

– Bill Slawski  
President, SEO by the Sea
